charterbusiness.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy| Charter Business

If you are commercial customer of Charter, a copy of the current commercial subscriber privacy policy is available here: [ Commercial Subscriber Privacy Policy ](http://www.charter.com/browse/content/your-privacy-rights).

## WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the website, any subdomains and its various related features (together referred to as the "site"). Charter Communications (referred to as "Charter," "us" or "we") is committed to protecting your privacy while on this site. Please read the information below to learn how we collect, use and disclose the information gathered by this site.

You acknowledge that by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions, or deletions shall become effective immediately upon posting. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this site and this Privacy Policy periodically, and to be aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the Privacy Policy as modified.

## Are You a Charter Customer?

This Privacy Policy only applies to your use of this site. This Privacy Policy does not govern Charter's treatment of information it collects, uses or discloses other than through this site. If you are looking for Charter's residential subscriber service agreement, acceptable use policy or other Charter residential subscriber policies, please click here: [ Charter Residential Subscriber Policies](http://www.charter.com/footer-page2/terms-of-service). If you are looking for Charter's commercial acceptable use policy or terms of service, please click here: [ Charter Commercial Subscriber Policies](http://www.charter.com/footer-page2/terms-of-service). If you are looking for Charter's cable television, Internet or telephone privacy policies, please click here: [ Charter Subscriber Privacy Policies](http://www.charter.com/footer-page2/terms-of-service). If you are a commercial customer of Charter, please consult your agreement or contact **800.314.7195** to speak with a Charter representative about how your information is used.

## Types of Information Collected

In order to provide this site and our numerous services, we collect two types of information on our site: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.

Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that identifies you specifically. When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering for a membership, ordering a product or service, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums or other public areas, entering a contest or sweepstakes, filling out a survey, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities; however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personally identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may also be asked to provide payment information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. This information is compiled and analyzed on both an individual and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, and your interactions while on our site. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a network, such as the World Wide Web. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web, allowing Web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet.

## Collection Methods and Use of Information

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you on this site unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us when you (a) register for our services and register your e-mail address with us; (b) enter sweepstakes or contests sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) sign up for special offers from us or from selected third parties; (d) send e-mail messages, submit forms, post to forums, or transmit other information by telephone, e-mail or letter; or (e) submit your payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our site. We may also collect information from you at other points on our site that state that such information is being collected.

In addition, we, or our third-party ad server, search provider and/or content server may collect, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers and/or software, to administer our site, and to gather demographic information. Our third-party ad servers may also provide us with reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon at our site.

We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information to (a) to provide our services to you, (b) to allow us to properly maintain this site and our services and to make improvements or upgrades when necessary, (c) to provide you with technical support and for system maintenance, (d) to inform you of new products or services that may be of interest to you, to respond to your inquiries or send administrative notices, (e) to prevent fraud, including the unauthorized use of this site or our services or violations of applicable policies and terms of service, or (f) to ensure our own compliance with the law. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our agreements with you, including any website terms of use or this Privacy Policy.

## Release of Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you have affirmatively agreed to such disclosure. Charter may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information with some of our same-branded affiliates for those affiliates' direct marketing purposes. We do provide some of our services or provide parts of this site through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners, and other third parties. We and our service partners may use your Personally Identifiable Information to deliver these services and to operate our site.

As part of our business activities, if we enter into a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of our assets, we may transfer your Personally Identifiable Information as part of the transaction.

Occasionally, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation or when otherwise permitted by applicable law. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use this site for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

## User Choices on Collection and Use of Information

If you do not wish to provide Personally Identifiable Information on this site, then you should not provide it when requested or otherwise provide your information to this site. However, some parts of this site or our service may not function without the requested information. If you would like limit our use of your Non-Personally Identifiable Information to target advertisements on this site, please [click here](https://connect.charter.com/cas/portal/settings/charterweboptout.aspx). We may, from time to time, send you marketing messages (e.g., email, direct mail, telephone calls, etc.) regarding our products and services. If you do not want to receive these marketing messages from Charter Business, please follow the opt-out instructions in the message or send your Charter Business opt-out request by calling 1- 800-314-7195.

## Security of Information

Charter takes the security of your Personally Identifiable Information seriously. We take such actions as are reasonably necessary to prevent unauthorized access by entities other than Charter to Personally Identifiable Information. Charter uses security and/or encryption technology to secure certain sensitive Personally Identifiable Information when it collects such information over this site. Charter restricts access to its customer database and secures the content by use of firewalls and other security methods. Charter limits access to databases containing Personally Identifiable Information to authorized employees and agents of Charter and other parties identified in the use and release sections above.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

You need to help protect the privacy of your own information. You should not give Personally Identifiable Information to strangers or others whom you are not certain have a right or need to the information. You also must take precautions to protect the security of any Personally Identifiable Information that you may transmit by using encryption and other techniques to help prevent unauthorized persons from intercepting or receiving any of your Personally Identifiable Information. You are responsible for the security of your information when using unencrypted, open access or otherwise unsecured networks in your home or elsewhere. Charter will never ask you to provide account sign-in passwords, credit card numbers, or other sensitive information through unsolicited email messages. If we request such information from you, we will always direct you to Charter's website. You should, however, be aware of imposter websites pretending to be Charter's. If you have received an email requested that you sign in or provide information that you suspect was not sent by Charter, DO NOT CLICK ON THE LINK IN THE EMAIL but use your own browser to go to Charter's site. If you are directed to a website that you not believe is Charter's, please contact Charter at 1- 800-314-7195 or forward the full email (with full Internet headers) to phishing@charter.net. Charter will also not ask for you Internet account password over the telephone.

## Cookies

When you use our site we may store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Our cookies may store Personally Identifiable Information and/or Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, your computer, or your preferences so that you may more easily use our site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly, and help us to maintain a more secure site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly in that case.

We partner with one or more third-party service providers to display advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they may place a separate cookie on your computer or utilize other means such as, web beacons, clear GIFs, pixel tags or other similar technologies, to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visit to our site and to target advertisements for our products and services. We and our third-party service provider will collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server, your interaction with our products and services, and whether you responded to a particular ad. If you would like more information about how we target advertisements on this site and to know your choices about not having this Non-Personally Identifiable Information used by our third-party service providers for this purpose, please [click here](https://connect.charter.com/cas/portal/settings/charterweboptout.aspx). Other advertisers may also place banner ads on our site in the same manner as above, but we will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information to them. Because a "Do Not Track" protocol has not yet been finalized, this site's information collection and disclosure practices, and the choices that it provides to you, will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received.

## Links to Third-Party Sites

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use, and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies which place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

## Note to California Customers Regarding Your Privacy Rights

California law requires Charter provide to you, upon request, certain information regarding the sharing of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As mentioned above, Charter does not share personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. However, Charter may share personally identifiable information with some same-branded affiliates for those affiliates' direct marketing purposes. If you make a request by using the below Website Privacy methods of contact, Charter will provide you with the number of its same-branded affiliates in California and a list of personal information that it may have shared with some or all such same-branded affiliates.

## Miscellaneous Privacy Issues

We use a third party provider to place our internet ads. The provider may collect anonymous information about your visits to our site and your interaction with our products and services. The provider may also use information about your visits to this and other sites to target advertisements for merchandise and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. The provider does not know your name, address, phone number, email address or any of your other personally identifiable information. If you would like more information about this practice and your option to not have this anonymous information used by our third party provider, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed) . To opt-out of these ads click on this [link](http://media.charter.com/optout.html).

This site is direct towards adults and you must be at least 18 years old to submit any Personally Identifiable Information to this site. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors that are under 18 years of age.

You should also be aware that when Personally Identifiable Information is voluntarily disclosed (i.e. your name, e-mail address, etc.) in any discussion forums or other public areas on this site, that information, along with any information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and this Privacy Policy does not apply to such information. Any submissions to public areas on this site are accepted with the understanding that they are accessible to all third parties. If you do not want your comments to be viewed by third parties, you are advised not to make any submissions. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of this site, please contact us by sending a letter or email to:

Charter Communications   
Attn: Legal Department, Website Privacy   
12405 Powerscourt Drive   
Saint Louis, Missouri 63131   
privacy (at) charter.com

If you have any questions about our services, your dealings with this site or to contact someone about the services offered by Charter Business, please contact us by calling 1- 800-314-7195.

Effective: December 16, 2013
